<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CampusPaths</string>
	<string name="main_title">CampusPaths</string>
   	<!-- Main screen -->
    <string name="route">Route</string>
    <string name="go">GO!</string>
    <string name="favorites">My Places</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    
    <string name="temp">Temp</string>
    
    <string name="darBase">Darwin Basement Floor Plan</string>
    <string name="darRmDest">Room 31 is in the basement of Darwin</string>
	<string name="newPath">New Path</string>
	
	<string name="buildingHint">Building Name</string>
	<string name="favs_title">My Places</string>
	<string name="edit_favs">Edit Places</string>
	<string name="save_favs">Save Places</string>
	<string name="places1">Place #1</string>
	<string name="places2">Place #2</string>
	<string name="places3">Place #3</string>
	<string name="places4">Place #4</string>
	<string name="places5">Place #5</string>
		
	<string name="start">Start</string>
	<string name="end">End</string>
	
	<string name="about_text"><b>Welcome to CampusPaths!</b>"\n"
	    This app is dedicated to helping you get around campus easier than ever before. "\n\n"
	    To begin simply choose your beginning and ending destinations, then press \"GO!\" The subsequent screen will give you three route options optimized to get you to your destination the quickest and easiest."\n\n"
	    Tap the marker over a Begin or End destination to view the precise location of that room. 
	    You can also save "Places," so you'll never again have to worry about finding that crumpled up post it note you wrote your scheduleon."\n"
	    To do this, simply open up the menu and press \"Edit Places\". This will take you to a screen where you can choose from all the locations on campus."\n\n"
	    <b>ABOUT THE TEAM</b>"\n"
	    Jolie Nazor - Jolie kept the team organized and on track, coordinating meetings and checkpoints, as well as contributing lots of essential code."\n"
	    Micah Gemmell - Micah has worked with android apps before, so he was the team\'s consultant and head programmer."\n"
	    Lauryn Loudermilk - Lauryn did whatever Jolie told her to do. Her main role in the project was getting the databse up and working but she also worked on UI."\n"
	    Mark Griffith - Mark is in charge of graphics and images for the app. Aren\'t they beautiful?"\n"
	    Jake Neugass - Jake came up with the concept for the app, and programmed much of the critical logic needed to make the app function."\n"
	    </string>	
</resources>